I have traveled across the globe for you
guys. I've came all the way to Australia
to find the right prop firm for you
guys. [music] And these weren't my
intentions originally.
About 4 weeks ago, I made 700k on FOMC
and this position had the potential to
make two, three million dollars. I just
cut it short. And I did a viral reel
that was basically calling out any
trader that could out trade me.
Not going to lie, it was a little bit of
an impulsive decision with this post,
but I was very confident in my decision.
If you believe that you can out trade
me, come to my trading floor, and please
out trade me.
And in the middle of all that, I got
thousands of DMs that a lot of people
said that there is an unfair advantage
to the way I trade and the regular
trader that is just trading their own
couple of hundred, maybe even their own
couple of thousand dollar account, that
they could never out trade me because
there's a giant enormous gap [music] and
lack of capital. They could never out
trade me because they just don't have
the capital that I do. And that got me
thinking a little bit and I realized how
disconnected I am from the access that I
have to the capital right now. I've been
trading for 7 years now, about going on
8 years now, and I haven't really came
across the idea of a lack of capital.
Like that doesn't really come across my
mind because I've had capital for a very
long time before I worked here at
Archer.
So, you guys put me on a mission to find
the right prop firm to work with. A prop
firm that has no hidden rules, a prop
firm that has no consistency rules,
that's regulated, and it has a real team
behind that it's not just a couple guys
in their home office just building a
business. It's a real team behind this,
so there's strategies with the data that
you use.
And you fast forward 4 weeks and I'm
here in Australia, where I have gone to
the office of one of the industry
leading prop firms, and I have asked all
the hard questions as to what makes this
prop firm different and why should
traders trade on it. So, when I were to
host a trading competition with traders
at my trading floor and someone can
attempt to out-trade me, they have a
fair equal edge exactly how I think. So,
it is a little surreal that I am here in
Australia right now, and this is a
decision that was made
in like 2 or 3 weeks, because I was
literally at Jake Paul's ranch
celebrating July 4th, 250th anniversary
of America, having a great time, and I
left that celebration early to come to
Australia and do this 26-hour journey
here. Because I can't imagine being in a
position right now where traders have
such a massive opportunity in front of
them, where they can really make a full
living out of trading and they don't
have to go to work. They don't have to
continuously be in debt. They don't have
to listen to someone or go clock in
somewhere. They can just learn a skill
set, use somebody else's money, and make
a living out of it. And
I I simply cannot fathom that traders
would spend 2 3 months attempting to
pass a prop firm account, and what would
happen is these prop firms would deny
them from a payout, or they would just
breach their accounts with these hidden
rules. And I wasn't really fully aware
of this because I just simply don't
trade prop firm accounts. I've been
trading personal accounts successfully
for the last 4 years and I've scaled
like that. And realizing this and that
it's been a very big bottleneck in the
industry and as to why majority of
traders can't succeed, it's because it's
almost like if they're being set up for
failure with the way these prop firms
are set up with all these hidden rules,
and basically everything set out
basically to get them. And when this
This brought to my attention in this
scope of the last four weeks. I I almost
had like a what the [__] moment because
how can traders spend so many hours
learning how to trade, putting in the
work to understand a skill set, and at
the end of it when they go put that
skill set to the test, they don't get
rewarded for it because a prop firm
wants to have more profit margin? That
didn't make any sense to me. I found it
extremely unethical. So, that's where
the motive and the drive for this really
became
it it it just lit a fire in me to
actually do this the correct way. And
it's almost like a full circle moment
because when I started in trading, I
started trading personal accounts. I
tried to become a successful trader
flipping these small accounts, and when
I had a
big flip, I would consider that I was
profitable and successful, and I was
very wrong. That was not the case at
all. That's not how you become a
successful trader. It's building
consistent profits, and I stumbled
across a prop firm. I took 20, 30
different prop firms. I blew them. I'll
give you guys the story now, but the the
backbone of my success is learning how
to pass a challenge, and when I pass it,
I get paid. I could I I I just can't
believe that traders are in a world
right now where they pass a challenge,
and there is an uncertainty that they
might not get paid.
>> [music]
>> So, when I mention that I really get and
understand what you guys are going
through, I mean very much so.
When I started and I came across
trading, I was a fresh high school
graduate, and I went to college. So, I
was in community college out of
commitment for my parents. So, I'm sure
like many of you guys out there, if you
don't have a college degree for your
parents, you're technically a failure.
And the problem is that our parents
don't understand that the way things how
they used to work back in the day aren't
how things work nowadays. You don't need
a degree to be successful in life or to
be somebody in life. You can figure out
different ventures that make money.
So, I struggled with that communication
back and forth with my parents, but to
avoid the arguments, my 18-year-old self
fresh out of high school, I said, "You
know what? I'm just going to go to
college, make my parents happy, and I'll
figure out what I want to do later."
Halfway through the semester, I'll never
forget my professor came up to me. I was
half asleep sitting on my desk, and he
said, "Hey Alex, look. Just letting you
know, no hard feelings, but if you were
to ace every single test from this point
forward, you would still fail. So, it's
better if you don't come back."
And I sat there, and I was like, "What
do you mean? If I were to ace every
single test, I failed. So, does that
mean that I would have to start again?
Do I get a different try at this? Can I
go to summer school?" He basically
looked at me. He's like, "No. You
failed. You have to come back next
semester. You just wasted your time."
Now, at that point, I got into a little
bit of panic because I just didn't
believe that I had to go up to my
parents and tell them, "Hey,
Mom, Dad, I failed college, and I don't
plan to go back." That conversation
frightened me because, like many of you
guys may experience if you have Latin
parents or immigrant parents that go to
the United States, they risk everything
that they had back in their home country
to give their kids an opportunity to
succeed. They do everything for the
kids. So, my dad went to America in a
raft from Cuba with 7 days stuck at sea,
very similar to my mom's story. And my
dad, all he cared about was that I went
back home with a degree.
And if I didn't go back home with a
degree, I was a failure.
So, for the rest of the semester, I
decided to not tell my parents, and I
would just still continuously go to
campus, but I would sit around the
library, the lunch area, and figure out
what solution I was going to tell my
parents that I came up with as to why I
dropped out of college and how I was
going to be successful. But the biggest
problem was that I really only had about
3 months to figure out what I was going
to tell my parents because they had my
location and like many of you guys know,
if again, you are coming from an
immigrant family, they want to make sure
that their kids are going to school,
doing what they're supposed to be doing
and my parents were tracking me on my
phone. So, I would still have to go to
campus every single day. Until one day,
I was sitting in the library near the
lunch area and one of my high school
friends named Brian. He came up to me
and he was like, "Hey, what's up, bro?
Haven't seen you since high school. I
actually did not join at the first part
of the semester because I've been
working on
this journey of an entrepreneur that was
going to make me rich."
And I'm like, "Well,
it kind of sounds like what I need right
now. So, tell me a little bit more,
Brian." Brian sits down, we chat back
and forth for about an hour, 2 hours,
and then he tells me what he's doing.
And he tells me that he's trading.
So, this is how I came across trading. I
came across trading from my friend
Brian.
And Brian says to me, "Hey, look Alex,
just to let you know, there's a group of
us that we're going to meet up at a
different college where we're going to
talk about trading and different
opportunities in the market that can
make us money this week, next week, and
then next month. You're going to learn
how to trade."
I'm like, "Really? How much is it going
to cost?" At this time, 2018, 2019,
trading wasn't super popular. It was
still very early days. You didn't really
see much on social media. You heard
about it, but it wasn't in your face
like how it is today.
And I decided, "You know what? Let's do
it. When do we have to go?" He said,
"We'll go tomorrow." So, the next day,
proceed to meet Brian and all of his
trader friends at this next college
campus and when I get there, there was
probably 80 other people.
And honestly, this was kind of cool at
first because I'm like, "Wow, I'm not
the only kid fresh out of high school
that doesn't want to go to college and
wants to figure out a different way how
to make money." So, it was very cool
seeing other people that were
like-minded and that understood me,
because in the other college campus, I
was just being around regular people
that what they did was go to school, get
the degree, and set themselves up for
9:00 to 5:00, and they were miserable at
life, and they didn't have big
aspirations. I've always wanted to be
hyper-successful and live a luxurious
life.
And I never forget that when I get
there, I see other like-minded people,
but it wasn't the entire truth. When I
got there, we didn't talk about trading
once. Everybody was talking about
recruiting people and signing people up.
And at first glance, I'm like, "Well,
maybe we need to recruit more people, so
more people look at the charts, and we
can find better opportunities." And I
didn't know I was walking right into one
of the biggest multi-level marketing
schemes that the industry had seen at
that time, which was iMarkets Live MLM.
Majority of you guys watching this video
right now probably have no idea what
this is. And if you do, you're an OG,
and you guys probably went through the
exact same thing as me.
But what this company consisted of was
just bringing people on board to pay a
monthly subscription to just bring
somebody else on board, and it was a
multi-level tier, and the catch was
trading, which is a very attractive
product for people to go out and cold
call people to sell.
I was there for about 2 to 3 weeks,
tried to figure out if anybody in this
circle knew how to trade. Nobody knew
how to trade, and I left the whole MLM
multi-level marketing scheme,
because I just did not want to do that.
I wanted to learn how to trade, because
I saw the opportunity of trading was
right there in front of me, but I didn't
know how to learn at that point, and
nobody there cared to learn, because
everybody was so focused on signing up
more people.
So, what I did was take that moment of
realizing what trading is and the
opportunity that it has, and then I
started figuring out how to do it
myself. I went back to the other college
campus with about 30 days left before
the semester ended, and I would sit at
the same exact spot every single day in
the library opening up dozens of YouTube
videos, Reddit reports. I was looking on
Google, I was looking on forums, any
possible way for me to understand how
trading works and how I can figure out
an edge. I spent hours watching scalping
videos, day trading videos, swing
trading videos, institutional anything
that was on the internet, I was
watching.
And all of this until I finally took my
first trade.
And I never forget, I took my first
trade on I think it was a $50 account
that I deposited.
And these $50 that I deposited from the
moment that I clicked the position, I
was already in drawdown. I was in a
loss.
Automatically panicked. I was probably
in drawdown
a couple cents.
And I panicked. I immediately closed out
the position and said, "I'm already
losing money and I haven't even done one
day of trading." Well, I didn't know at
the time that there was a cost to trade.
You have spread, you have commission,
and the problem was that I was by
myself. I was self-teaching myself and
self-learning myself. And whatever
mistake that I made, I had to figure out
if it was a mistake for good or for bad.
And from what I remember, I think that
trade that I took would have made me a
little bit of money. I don't really
remember specifically, it was a very
long time ago. But what I do remember is
taking another trade and another trade
and another trade
until I eventually
blew my account.
And that was not my first account that I
blew, but that was my first loss. And
And said, "You know what?
It's fine.
50 bucks, it's not a big deal. I got
some savings. Worst case, I can ask my
parents for a little bit of money saved
for school, saved for something, and I'm
sure I could get it." I wasn't worried
about the 50-dollar loss at that time.
Because I've always had an entrepreneur
mindset where I understand that you have
to put something at risk to get
something. So, I'm like, "Okay, I'll
lose these 50 bucks because the next
trade that I take will make me back 50
bucks." It's almost like that gambler's
fallacy that needs to lose two times in
order to win, like if there is some type
of
system behind it.
And then came the second loss, then the
third loss, fourth loss, fifth loss.
And the losses didn't stop.
Faster than I realized, I had lost
probably 5,000 dollars. Now, at this
point in my journey, I'm still in
college, not going to college for a
degree. I'm going because my parents are
tracking my location, and I need to show
them that I'm still going to school.
And I'm on a time clock because I need
to figure out a solution to tell my
parents what I'm doing and why I didn't
graduate college when I had to go get my
diploma, why I don't have a diploma.
And I remember at this point where I was
so committed to this journey that I had
no other choice but to continue to do
this. I had to continue to trade in
order to at least make back this loss
because there's no way I was going to
waste two, three months of my journey
and then just simply
waste it and not make anything back out
of it.
So, then I proceed to lose 5,000
dollars, 10,000 dollars, 15,000 dollars.
And then I was negative 28,000 dollars.
This is money that I had from my savings
account. This is money that I had from
my parents' account. This is money that
I got on credit cards. 28,000 dollars I
I negative in my trading. And I remember
at this point, I was scared because
obviously that's a lot of money, but at
no point that I doubt that I was going
to make it back. I didn't know if it was
going to be through trading or if it was
going to be somewhere else, but I knew I
was going to figure out a way how I was
going to make this money back. Now, this
changed from oh, I need to show my
parents that I'm successful with
something and I need to
exchange the college degree with this
other business. No, I I first need to
make this money back. So, my my entire
focus shifted towards that. And that's
when I came across prop firms. So, let
me explain how prop firms changed things
for me entirely. [music] Shall we?
So, $28,000
of a loss later
and working at Dunkin' Donuts, I knew I
needed to find a solution how to do this
and it had to be done through trading.
So, this is when I was working at
Dunkin' Donuts just to start slowly
recovering, making back this loss, but I
did the math. It would have taken me 2
years to make this back.
And this is where everything changed.
While working at Dunkin' Donuts, I came
across a prop firm.
This is when prop firms were not a
thing, right? Everything was very
skeptical in the industry because it was
the first time anybody's ever used it.
And the way a prop firm worked back
then, [music] it was very simple. Two
steps. Step one, make 10% in 30 days.
Step two, make 8% [music] in 60 days.
And you have 8% stop loss, 10% stop
loss, and that is it. Very simple, but
nobody has ever really done it.
And like the novice trader that I was at
the time and that I was willing to take
a risk, I went and took my first
challenge being at $28,000 in drawdown.
So, imagine being in a loss, working at
a 7:00 to 3:00. I didn't work a 9:00 to
5:00. I actually I believe is the
hardest schedule, 7:00 to 3:00, cuz you
have to wake up at 5:30 in the morning,
6:00 in the morning to make it to work
by 7:00. And
I realized that when I took this
challenge, I understood what trading
was, but I didn't have an edge in the
market. I wasn't profitable at the time.
I understood how to identify certain key
points, why the market is heading up,
why it's heading down, but I was still
very much a student of the game, very
early student of the game.
Took my first 100K challenge, like every
novice trader would do. I'm sure you
guys have made the same mistake, that
the first account you want to get into
the prop firm wants to be [music] the
biggest account, because you want to
manage the most amount of money the
fastest way possible.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> And that was probably the biggest
mistake, because I had just come from
losing $28,000 on small increments, you
know, $500 deposit here, $1,000 deposit
here, $2,000 deposit here, $500 deposit
here. And I never really understood what
it was to trade larger accounts. So,
when I got my first 100K account, and I
took my first position that I risked
$2,000, I I was so dumbfounded when I
lost those $2,000, because I thought the
game was over at that point, because
that's what the entire size account was
for my personal account. But then when I
realized that it was only 2% of the big
account, kind of opened my eyes a little
bit. I'm like, well,
the more money you have in trading, the
less dollar amount you could risk to
make a high dollar amount. It's on a
percentage game. This is where things
started to change. Obviously, my first
account blew it. Straight up from the
second trade, I risked all of it, blew
the account.
But it's fine, because it opened up my
eyes to something else. More money
equals less risk dollar-wise, which
means better type of trades. Slowly
started to understand what it was to be
somewhat of a profitable trader.
And then I'll never forget, I ended up
probably blowing 10 more challenges and
this is in a
ratio of probably a month.
And probably on month three or month
four, I made a little bit of money on
personal accounts, did a little bit of
side hustles here, worked two jobs. I
worked at the fair riding people on
bicycles from the fair to their parking
spot. Washed cars, worked at Crocs, did
so many different types of side hustles
to just make more money so I can bring
down that depth and figure out a way on
how to tell my parents again that I am
not going to college and that I am going
to be
trader.
Keep in mind, I still haven't seen any
profit from trading.
So, this is where about two and a half
years into the journey. So, I was about
a year and a half two years losing just
personal accounts and then I was six
months trading prop firm accounts.
I finally passed the challenge. So,
around month five of trading prop firms,
I passed stage one. So, I was four to
five consecutive months just losing
challenge after challenge after
challenge, but always getting slightly a
little bit closer and making a different
mistake than what I did the last time.
But most importantly, I would simply
[music] bring out my notepad, write it
down, and not do it the next time. When
you learn from so many of your losses
and so many lessons, it will get to the
point where things will start to turn if
you are smart enough and you actually
apply the lessons that you have learned.
So, around month four or month five, I
passed my stage one, passed my stage
two, and I get to the funded stage. I
almost get to the funded stage and I was
confused. I couldn't believe that I was
finally a funded trader on a 100K
account.
But I almost treated it as if it wasn't
super important.
And what I did was just continue to
trade.
What ended up happening after that
is what changed everything for me. I
made $28,000
on that 100k account. I took a
continuous repetitive exact same
position. I took GBP NZD breaking out
from the all-time lows. I'll never
forget that. I have pictures,
screenshots on my phone. I was taking
continuation trades on USD JPY,
continuous breaking retest, and just
holding, settling for getting letting
the trade run. And in that month, it it
it almost turned into a game of just
predicting the market, and the money was
just following. But I was doing this
almost numb to the money because it
almost it almost didn't feel real
because I had just
failed so many challenges and blown so
many accounts that it was just numbers
on the screen. It was exciting because
yeah, I was being right, but I I almost
didn't think I was going to get the
payout. I just said, you know, I'm I'm
actually getting good at trading.
And
you fast forward seven of these
different trades with 1:4
risk-to-rewards where everything
perfectly lined up, and I was in profit
I think I was in profit like $35,000.
And then I get my profit split. I
request it, excited,
still getting ready for this to
potentially not work,
and the money hits my bank account.
Exactly what I was in debt is exactly
what I just got in a payout in 1 month.
When I made $28,000 in a single month,
everything entirely changed for me. This
is where I'm like, okay,
I don't need Dunkin' Donuts ever in my
life again. I don't need to go work at
Crocs. I don't need to go ride people on
a bike from the fair to their parking
spot.
I just need to do what I just did right
now in trading and do it again.
And the next month, I decided to take
that same approach, use those exact same
principles, and I did it again. Had
another profitable month, had another
payout, and at this point in my journey
is where I knew I was going to be a
trader.
And I'm still working at Dunkin' Donuts.
I'm still telling my parents that I'm
going to college. I wanted to have a
very strong safety net because
in a Cuban household, if essentially you
don't go to college, you're a failure.
Your parents don't want you at the
house. They're not going to kick you out
of the house. They're not going to boot
you. They would just
force you in an uncomfortable way where
you would almost leave yourself. And I
had to prepare myself for that because I
knew I would have I'd have to go live by
myself. I would have to pay rent and
have my own bills. So, I changed my goal
from telling my parents, "Hey, I didn't
go to college. I did not get a degree.
And I failed essentially to I need to
save up 12 months of my monthly
expenses. So, when I do go have that
conversation, I'll tell Hey, look. Don't
worry. I've been working on this. I have
money. I'll show them in my bank
account. And if they don't believe me,
I'll make the step and move out and show
them that I'm committed. So, my motive
changed to instead of
figuring out a plan to what I was going
to do. Like this was the plan. It It
almost unfolded right in front of me.
And a lot of people, a lot of the time,
they want to plan their life. They want
to plan their journey, what they want to
do, their purpose, you know, and all
that's great to have goals and have
organization in your life, but sometimes
the best things just happen right in
front of you and then you just need to
realize it and make the most out of it.
So, I'll never forget. I think I have
saved up 40, 50 thousand dollars in my
bank account. I'm still working at
Dunkin' Donuts at this point. Still
having to deal with my boss.
And on my third payout, I think I
roughly got
I think it was like 10,000 dollars on my
third payout. I decided to do an
expedited withdrawal. At the time you
could do that. And uh what ended up
happening was that I wanted to double
down on the account, make more risk so I
can get to that 100k.
And I blew my funded account.
So, I was profitable [music] for 3
months, withdrawing every single month,
paying back my debt, and having savings
account. So, when I go talk to my
parents, and [music]
I blow my funded account.
When I blew my funded account, I almost
didn't think it was real. Like, wait.
I'm like the best. I just was profitable
for 3 months that every single trade is
going in my favor. How did I just blow
it?
That's where I had the moment of
realization. I'm like, oh,
this doesn't mean just because you are a
funded trader that you're profitable for
life. Doesn't mean this is this is not
like college. Like, once you get a
diploma, once you get your degree,
doesn't mean that you are now that
person forever. This is very different.
You can be a profitable trader today,
and you can be an unprofitable trader
tomorrow if you start to break your
rules and do things that an unprofitable
trader doesn't do.
I'm like, whoa. Okay, that was a moment
of realization. My ego, my emotions got
to me at that point because what
happened is I got overconfident. I
thought I was an invincible, and I
thought that once you get that title of
being an a profitable trader that that
holds forever.
No, you can definitely lose that if
you're doing the wrong things that
didn't lead you to get to that very
point at that very time.
So, at this point,
probably have $60,000 saved up. Try some
more prop firm accounts, blow two three
more of these accounts. Start to feel a
little bit shaky in the journey, and I
decide to just put some money into my
personal account at the same time that I
trade the prop firm accounts. Pass a
prop firm account, scale a little bit my
personal account, and then eventually
get another payout about 2 months later,
and I reach the point where I have
$100,000 in profit. Now, that change
that I went from profitable to
unprofitable was very short-lived
because I knew exactly what I did to be
a profitable trader, and I knew the
exact mistakes that I did that led me to
be an unprofitable trader again. All I
had to do was just switch right back to
what I was doing. Sticking to my risk
management, taking quality over quantity
trades, pro-trend trades, no
counter-trend trades, and most
importantly the risk management. Not
trying to chase that million-dollar day
right from the start when you don't have
the account that backs it.
So, got back, funded account, got
another payout, and got to the point
where I saved about
dollars, which was lit way more than
what my monthly expenses were at the
time.
And the time came to tell my parents my
plan, or what I had been doing. And this
is where things changed a little bit.
And believe [clears throat] me,
this was kind of expected.
>> [sighs]
>> So, my parents had to tell my parents
that I was not going to college for the
last couple of months. I had failed, but
I had figured out a different way to
make money.
Now, my parents did not hear anything
other than I did not go to college. I
did not care that I was making money,
did not care that I was doing a
business. They had no interest in any of
that.
And they have even less interest when I
told them what I was doing was trading.
They looked at me like if I was speaking
Chinese.
Trading, what is that? Is that la bolsa
de valore? Cuz my parents don't speak
English. It's like, is this when money
goes up and down? You're going to lose
all your money because back in the day
what my parents are used to is 2008,
Wall Street went down. That's what they
think when they think investments or
trading.
And uh
their support was even less. Their care
was even less. It was The disappointment
was uh
even worse than what I expected. But,
luckily, I had prepared for myself for
that. I was ready to literally pack my
bags at that very moment and go to my
own place. Simply because I was going to
be in an environment where my parents
every single day were going to be down
my neck, "Why am I not doing this? I'm
not going to be successful." And as a
trader, as you guys may know, 90% of
trading really comes down to how you are
when you are trading in the markets. Are
you mentally stable? Do you have your
emotions in check? Are you ready to not
be greedy? Are you trading based off of
the markets, not how you feel? Like,
that influences significantly in your
results. Because if you have any
instability in your emotions, so does
your trading. So, at that very moment, I
think a week or two later, got my stuff,
moved to my own place, and my parents
didn't support me still then. But, they
had a reality moment. They're like,
"Wait. He has enough money to go live by
himself.
He'll be back next month. He'll be back
in a couple of months." And if you move
out of your At least in my household, if
you move out of your parents' home and
you come back, you are even You're a
mega failure because you couldn't go do
it by yourself. You have to go back to
your parents' nest. So, I made sure I
prepared myself so strong for that. Move
out by myself in my own apartment, and
this is where everything just really,
really started growing for me. I started
to double down on my personal and prop
firm accounts. I started scaling and
stacking prop firm accounts on top of
prop firm accounts. And I started aiming
for bigger quality trades. So, I wasn't
aiming to have big home runs. I was
waiting all week for that perfect trade
and being a sniper and executing when
that opportunity was right in front of
me and it was extremely obvious. I
wasn't really going out looking for
trades. I was awaiting for the trades to
come to me. I was missing a load of
opportunities, but I was also avoiding a
load amount of losses. And if I would
have taken both the wins and losses, I
would be profitable by the end of it,
but with extra mental damage and
emotional damage by the week, and I just
tried my best to make trading as simple
as possible. And this is where I started
to get busy by just posting videos on
social media, and things started to
change. People started to watch me on
what I was doing. I started to trade
live with people, and I was actually
educating people when I was just doing
what I was doing. And this is how all
this happened out of nowhere, but all
because I decided to take that risk by
trading a prop firm account. And I
decided to give it a shot because I had
ran out of capital for myself. With the
prop firm account,
I learned how to manage risk. I learned
how to follow rules when nobody is
watching. Because even on my own
personal account nowadays, I break the
rules, but I'm okay with it. But with a
prop firm, the moment you break a rule,
you lose your account. So, there's a
software in place that is always
supervising you to make sure you follow
your rules. It teaches you how to manage
larger amounts of capital. This large
amount of capital is how real traders
trade. What I understood out of this is
where my trading changed drastically.
Bought my first supercar, bought my
first Rolex, bought my first Richard
Mille, bought my next hypercar, bought
two Bugattis, bought a plane. All of
this started to come when I stuck to
these core foundations and scaled this
as time went on. It did not come
overnight. You know, many of you guys
may be seeing this right now and like,
"Oh, I want to be where Alex is right
now." And you are looking at the top of
the iceberg. Like there's so much that
was built throughout this journey that
it didn't come from a perfectly executed
plan. I made many of mistakes throughout
the way. I've blown many accounts. I've
lost many challenges, but I've never
lost the vision of being a successful
trader. And in order for you to become a
successful trader, you have to become a
successful trader. In order for things
in your life to change, you have to
change things in your life. You can't
have bad habits. You can't be around bad
people. You can't not have a strategy.
Without a strategy, you're simply not
going to execute the trades on a funded
account the correct way. And what I
really want you to understand from this
is that
if it worked for me, it can work for
you.
There is nothing that I have special. I
don't have 10 fingers. I don't have
four arms. I am just simply somebody
that decided to learn a skill set, add a
source like a powerful tool like prop
firms to this skill set, and stick to it
as long as I possibly could, and not let
anything get in between of me and what I
want to do. And you have it a lot easier
because you have people like me. There's
dozens of people like me showing their
story, and you're being able to actually
follow it more frequently. There's lives
now. There's multiple platforms of
social media. When I got started, none
of that existed. It was really just me
versus me. Now, the people that are
complaining nowadays that they can't do
it because it's too hard, it's better if
you just stop. This is not meant for
you. This is really meant for someone
that is ready to actually put in the
work and go through a journey. Because
the journey is what's going to build you
to where you want to be. Copying signals
and copying traders trades off of
whatever random post will not lead you
to profitability because the moment that
goes away, you don't know how to manage
your own risk. You don't know how to
follow rules when no one's watching, and
you don't know simply know how to do it
for yourself. So,
if I did it for myself back in the day
when none of this was available, why
can't you? You have all the possible
resources to do this yourself today.
That's why I'm building a trading floor.
I'm building a trading floor to make
this even more resourceful for people to
come to my space privately, it's an
invitation only, but they have a place
where they can meet other like-minded
people, and they can engage with traders
that are in the exact same journey as
them. We're building a small hedge fund,
internal funds, and internal
competitions there because that is what
leads a trader to scale without them
even realizing that they're developing a
better skill set in their trading with
the skill set that they use with prop
firm accounts, with personal accounts,
around other successful traders. And the
main reason why I came here to Australia
is to find that prop firm. That prop
firm that gives you guys those fair
market conditions, gives you guys no
hidden rules, gives you guys ethical
challenges where they're not set to
basically fail you. And you guys heard
it from the founders themselves, if you
guys haven't seen my latest video. It's
designed for traders to build consistent
profits. That's why there is profit cap
rules, that's why there's certain rules
that are right in front of you. There's
no hidden rules, and they're there to
this They're They're They're for traders
to be trading, not for traders to just
come and make money. The problem with
the trading industry and what it has
shifted to and what it's brought
is the people that want to just make
money. They don't want to earn the
money. So, they want to show up to
trading, punt a full portrait on gold or
any volatile pair, and make as much
money as possible so they can use that
money to pay off their debt, and buy
whatever they want to buy. I get it. You
want to make the money because you're in
a tough situation. But, this is not an
industry where you're going to just make
money and leave. This is an industry
where you need to learn the skill set,
and you will consistently earn money.
You need to change your mindset to
making money to pay off debt to I'm
going to learn the skill set, I'm going
to earn profits, and I can do this
consistently so I don't have to race or
have stress that I need this money
tomorrow. It's not a place where you're
just going to get lucky or catch a
winning streak that's going to change
your life because those big wins is not
what you can do consistently. Those big
wins come random. They're not
predictable. So, you can't depend your
success your journey on these big wins
and you need to shift your mindset to
earning these profits. It's what I love
about this proper and it really doubles
down on what I believe in, which is
consistency, sticking to your same
rules, sticking to your exact same
strategy, and most importantly, using
risk management. That's why I came out
here to Australia,
meet up with them and hosted a meet and
greet out here in person. I asked the
other traders what do they want to see
from these platforms, what rules do they
want to do, and it was very refreshing
to get this take of the industry once
again simply because I forgot. I really
did forget what this was like because
I've just been trading on my own
personal accounts with my own personal
rules. But, it's very refreshing to see
that we have just found a new fresh
space in the industry that traders can
actually capitalize off of the ethical
way. So, now with that being said, I
hope you guys enjoyed this video. This
is a real story, real moments that
happened in my life, and I'm sure you're
going through something very similar
right now. I encourage you to just keep
going. If I did it, so can you. There's
no reason why you shouldn't be where you
want to be as long as you're doing
things correctly. Don't rush the
process. Everything happens for a
reason.
Thank you guys very much for watching
this video. Hope you like, comment, and
subscribe on this and I'll see you guys
in the next one. Oh, and by the way,
before you click off this video and hit
that like, and comment, and subscribe, I
want you to tell me in the comments down
below why you aren't succeeding in your
journey. I I want to know because
the first reason that I receive from
traders is that they can't out trade me
because they have a lack of capital.
Okay, now we have the proper platform
for that. Now, what else? What is
holding you back from passing the
challenge and become a funded trader? Is
it your strategy? Is it your emotions?
Is it how you manage? Just tell me down
below in the comments what it is so I
make a video to help you guys out.
Enjoy. See you guys later.